yashrajfilms.com 2019-04-17

# Privacy Policy - Yash Raj Films

This Privacy Policy sets out the manner in which http://www.yashrajfilms.com/ (hereinafter referred to as "Website") owned and operated by ‘Yash Raj Films Private Limited’ (hereinafter referred to as “YRF”, “We” or “Us” or “Our”) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from user(s) (“You “and “Yours”) on the Website and other related services. By accessing, availing and using the Website and/or any of the services, and in particular by subscribing to YRF Newsletter and/or creating an account on the Website (collectively referred to as ‘Services’), You are consenting to the use, transfer, storage, disclosure and other uses of Your information (including but not limited to personal and non-personally identifiable information) in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

Third party websites are not owned or controlled by YRF. YRF is not responsible for any third-party content, services, businesses, advertisements, and/or links or Your access to third-party site and services including but not limited to Facebook or Google+. This Privacy Policy does not apply to Third Party Services. You are encouraged to carefully read and understand the privacy policies of respective third-party services before You access such services.

### Information we may collect from You:

### Personally Identifiable information

Your personal information may be collected in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, information submitted when You subscribe to the Newsletter and/or create an account on the Website, wherein You may be asked to submit details like name, email address, mailing address, phone number and credit card information or Your profile information, Your bookmarked contents on the Website.

Further Personally Identifiable Information can be collected when You choose to open an account, participate in or access the Website and Services using third-party sites and services credentials including but not limited to Facebook or Google+ credentials. We may upon such access automatically collect certain information, such as Your name, picture, and email address. The manner of usage of such information gathered through third-party sites or services shall be subject to their respective policies and Your chosen preference on dealing with such credentials on respective third-party sites including but not limited to Facebook or Google+.

We will collect Your Personally Identifiable Information only if You voluntarily submit such information to Us. Registration with Us is optional. You can always refuse to supply Personally Identifiable Information, except that it may prevent You from accessing and engaging in certain Website and/or Service related activities which are available only to registered users.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

Non-Personally Identifiable Information is collected when You access or interact with our Website and/or Services. Non-Personally Identifiable Information includes but is not limited to browser name, version, the type of device used, users’ operating system and version, Your mobile devices unique device ID, third party apps or website or service that referred users to Our Website and/or Services, language preference, means of connection to any of Our Services users’ location information, Internet service providers, IP address, technical information and other similar information about users.

### Web browser cookies

We may upon Your consent (in cases of certain jurisdictions that require us to obtain your consent to use cookies) or otherwise place cookies on Your hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to identify information about Your activities. Whenever You access or interact with Our Website or any of the Services, We may use "cookies" to enhance Your experience or sometimes to personalise Your experience. These cookies, among other things, are used to identify the number of visits You make to Our website, Your browsing pattern on Our website and the duration of Your visits to Our website. You may choose to disable cookies by turning off the cookie feature on the web browser, which will prevent the web browser from accepting new cookies. Further, depending upon the sophistication of Your web browser software, You can set up an alert when cookies are being sent. Please note that by disabling the cookies, some parts of Our Website or any of the Services may not function properly. We do not have control over the cookies placed by third-party service providers.

### How we use the collected information

Your Personally Identifiable Information such as email address and password are used to identify You when You attempt to logging to Your account on the Website. Such information may be used to control and secure Your access to Your account on Our Website and any Services that You may request from time to time.

The information provided by You for registering to services on the Website may be used to communicate with You, customise Your experience of the Website and/or the content of any newsletter or other material that We may send to You occasionally or on selected period of time and/or use the information collected to respond to any of Your inquiries, questions, and/or any other requests or provide administrative information, changes in account settings, changes to Our services or update You on new policies, products or services and updates pertaining to Your subscriptions and/or Website and Services.

If You have subscribed to Our newsletter, We will send periodic emails based on Your interest, if any selected. If at any time You would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, detailed instructions for discontinuation of the subscription are included at the bottom of each email or You may contact us via Our Website.

### How We protect Your information

Appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures are adopted to protect against unauthorised access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of Your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Website. Nevertheless, We cannot guarantee the security of any information obtained through unauthorised entry or use, hardware or software failure, and other factors that may compromise the security of secured information at any time beyond the control of the YRF including but not limited to hacking, data theft, unauthorised access.

### Sharing Your personal information

We do not share, deal with or disclose Your information that we collect from You through the Website or Services to any third-parties, except as described in this Policy. However, generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information, for instance, information relating to number of visitors and users accessing the Website or Services, may be shared with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

Please note, at times, We may be required by law to disclose Your personal information in the good faith and belief that the disclosure is reasonably necessary to respond to court orders, or other legal process. Disclosure of information may also include instances where, in Our discretion, it may be necessary for national security, law enforcement, or other issues of public importance. We further reserve the right to transfer Your Personal Information to another party as a result of merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets to another party.

### Changes to this privacy policy

We reserve the right to revise, modify or change the Privacy Policy at any time without providing any prior written notice. All changes/revisions would become effective immediately upon being posted on the Website. You are encouraged to periodically check this page to stay informed about changes to Our Privacy Policy. Continued access and/or use of the Website and/or any of the Services following notice of any such changes will indicate Your acknowledgement of such changes and You will be bound by such revised Provisions. If You disagree with any of the provisions of the Privacy Policy, You should not access and use Website and/or Services.

### Contacting us

You can direct all Your questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this Website or Your dealings with this Website or any of the Services to: [helpdesk@yashrajfilms.com](mailto:helpdesk@yashrajfilms.com?Subject=Legal%20query%20from%20the%20YRF%20Website).

This document was last updated on 21 October 2016.
